coindump.biz 2018-09-18

# PRIVACY POLICY

COINDUMP TOKENS SALE
PRIVACY POLICY
     Last updated: 24.11.2017

STATUS AND ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY
1. This Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the “Policy”) sets forth the general rules of
Participant’s Personal Data collection, processing, distribution, use and keeping by
COINDUMP.
2. Throughout this Policy, COINDUMP will use the term “Personal Data” to describe
information that can be associated with a specific person (the Participant) and can be used to
identify that person (including the information about the Participant’s activities, such as
information about Your use of the Website, when directly linked to personally identifiable
information, including automatically collected). COINDUMP does not consider Personal Data to
include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific Participant.
3. This Policy is inalienable part of COINDUMP General Terms & Conditions of COINDUMP Tokens
Sale. In terms not regulated by this Policy, the COINDUMP General Terms & Conditions of
COINDUMP Tokens Sale shall apply to the relationships that arise hereunder.
4. The definitions set forth herein and mentioned with capital letter shall have the
meaning as described in COINDUMP General Terms & Conditions of COINDUMP Tokens
Sale.
5. It is presumed that by the fact of the Website use and purchase of COINDUMP Tokens or by
providing COINDUMP the Personal Data directly on its request, the Participant has fully read,
understood and accepted this Policy. If any Participant does not agree with this Policy in general
or any part of it, such Participant should withhold from using the Website and/or purchase of
COINDUMP Tokens.
COLLECTION, PROCESSING AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA
6. The purpose of personal data collection, storage and processing within the COINDUMP
project shall only be the identification of the COINDUMP Token purchaser – Participant of the
COINDUMP Tokens Sale.
7. COINDUMP collects Personal Data from running the Website and uses Personal Data, provided
to COINDUMP by You. When the Participant visits the Website or uses our products, COINDUMP
collects the Personal Data sent to COINDUMP by Your computer, mobile phone, or other access
device. This Personal Data includes:
   1) Your mobile network information;
   2) Your IP address;
   3) Information about the device that Participant uses to access the Website and/or COINDUMP
   App. Such information includes, but is not limited to, identifier, name, and type, operating
   system;
   4) Web log information, such as Your browser type, and the pages You accessed on COINDUMP
   Website.
When the Participant uses a location-enabled device with COINDUMP Website and products,
COINDUMP may collect geographical location data or use various means to determine the
location, such as sensor data from the Participant’s device that may, for instance, provide
data on nearby cell towers and Wi-Fi access spots. However, COINDUMP will not
                                                                                                1

release Your personally identifying information of such kind to any third party without Your
consent, except as set forth herein.
8. If the Participant wants to purchase COINDUMP Tokens, COINDUMP will collect and store the
following types of Personal Data about You:
      1) Your name;
      2) Your email.
9. In certain cases (when additional verification by bank or compliance authority is needed
according to governmental rules, anti-money laundering (AML) or “know-your-customer” (KYC)
policies) COINDUMP may require You to provide additional information, and namely:
      1) Your address;
      2) Date of birth;
      3) Passport or driver license details;
      4) Numbers that You may use or have registered with Your local tax authority;
      5) Utility bills;
      6) Photographs of You;
      7) Confirmation of proceeds sources;
      8) Sworn statements.
The abovementioned information and details shall be provided only upon special personal
request to the Participant and specified in respective email.
10. COINDUMP reserves it’s right to request basic Personal Data, described in clause 9, prior to
the purchase of COINDUMP Tokens and/or use of any services, available through the Website.
COINDUMP may refuse the Participant access to the Website in case if COINDUMP has
grounded doubts as to the validity, authenticity and genuineness of the Personal Data, provided
by the Participant.
11. If the Participant does not provide COINDUMP with the Personal Data as specified in clauses
8, 9. hereof, the Participant shall not be able to use the full functionality of the Website and
purchase COINDUMP Tokens and/or use the COINDUMP Application (“COINDUMP App”). At
that, COINDUMP shall not bear any liability for such possible incomplete use.
12. When the Participant accesses the Website or uses COINDUMP products or services
COINDUMP (or a service provider on our behalf) may place small data files called “cookies” on
the Participant’s computer or other device. COINDUMP uses these technologies to recognize You
as our Token Sale Participant, customize COINDUMP Website, COINDUMP App and advertising,
measure promotional effectiveness and collect information about Your computer (as described
in clause 7. hereof) or other access device to mitigate risk, help prevent fraud, and promote trust
and safety. You may control the use of cookies within Your internet browsers’ settings. If you
reject or delete certain cookies, be aware that the performance of the related features and
functions of our Website and services may be impaired.
13. COINDUMP collects from the Participants only the Personal Data that COINDUMP needs for
their proper use of the Website or for purchase of COINDUMP Tokens. In particular,
COINDUMP uses the Participant’s Personal Data to:
                                                                                                2

     1) Administer COINDUMP Website and COINDUMP App and provide services;
     2) Develop new products and services;
     3) Personalize COINDUMP Website and COINDUMP App for You;
     4) Send You technical notices, support and administrative messages;
     5) Communicate with You about products, services, promotions, events and other news and
     information COINDUMP may think will be of interest to You;
     6) Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with COINDUMP
     Website and COINDUMP App;
     7) Provide third parties with statistical information about COINDUMP Participants (but
     those third parties will not be able to identify any individual Participant from that
     information);
     8) Detect, investigate and prevent illegal activities within the COINDUMP App
     and the Website, as well as protect the rights and property of the COINDUMP and
     others;
     9) Link or combine Personal Data COINDUMP collects from or about You; and
     10) Verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of COINDUMP
     Website and COINDUMP App.
14. COINDUMP is the only data controller and processor, except for the cases when there is an
objective COINDUMP needs to control/process or store Personal Data at COINDUMP’s
counterparties or agents. Should such counterparty or agent be engaged by the COINDUMP,
COINDUMP shall notify You in advance.
15. You may access, review and edit Your Personal Data at any time by communicating
COINDUMP in writing.
16. The Participant has the right to require COINDUMP to delete Participant’s Personal Data
provided by the Participant to COINDUMP or revoke his (or her) consent for collection,
processing and storage of his (or her) personal data by COINDUMP at any time. If You decide
to do this, You should send the respective notification to the COINDUMP. COINDUMP shall
delete Your respective Personal Data from any sources within 24 hours from the moment
COINDUMP receive such request from You. At that, the COINDUMP reserves its right to
suspend provision of any services to You referring to COINDUMP project and/or delete Your
Account on the Website or the COINDUMP App without prior notice, not providing any
compensations to You.
17. COINDUMP will not publish any Personal Data related to Your purchase of COINDUMP
Tokens without Your prior written consent.
PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION AND SHARING
18. COINDUMP will do any and all efforts and actions prescribed by Applicable Law to store any
of Your personal data in secrecy.
19. COINDUMP stores and process Your Personal Data on COINDUMP servers in various
jurisdictions, where our facilities and/or COINDUMP service providers are located. By submitting
Your Personal Data, You agree to this transfer, storing, or processing. COINDUMP will take all steps
reasonably necessary to ensure that Your Personal Data is treated securely and in accordance with
this Policy. COINDUMP protects Your Personal Data under internationally acknowledged
standards,
                                                                                                3

using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse,
unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. Third parties may be located in other countries
where the laws on processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than in Your country. From
time to time, the Personal Data may be also stored in other locations, and in such cases,
COINDUMP will ensure that the Personal Data will be stored and processed with the reasonable
level of care and security.
20. COINDUMP will not share Your Personal Data with any third parties other than COINDUMP
respective identity verification partners. COINDUMP reserves it’s right to share Your Personal
Data with:
    1) COINDUMP banking and brokerage partners, if necessary;
    2) Companies that COINDUMP plans to merge with or be acquired by (should such a
    combination occur, COINDUMP will notify You and will require that the newly combined entity
    follow these terms with respect to Your Personal Data);
    3) Third party identification service providers for fraud prevention purposes;
    4) Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when COINDUMP are
    compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure; or COINDUMP
    believes in good faith that the disclosure of Personal Data is necessary to prevent physical
    harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of any of
    COINDUMP policies;
    5) COINDUMP Personal Data processing counterparties or agents, hired by or cooperating with
    us, who’s services are required by us from the practical point of view;
    6) Other third parties only with Your prior consent or direction to do so.
21. COINDUMP will not provide Your Personal Data to any other Website users or
third parties other than described in clause 20 herein without Your consent or direction.
22. COINDUMP will not sell or rent Your Personal Data to third parties.
23. COINDUMP may combine Your Personal Data with information COINDUMP collects from
other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Website and COINDUMP App, as well
as our content and advertising.
24. COINDUMP may use Your name and email address to provide You with information about
products or services that may be of interest to You, but COINDUMP will not use Your Personal
Data without complying with applicable laws and, where appropriate, obtaining your consent.
25. COINDUMP services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our
partner networks, advertisers, and affiliates (including, but not limited to, websites on which the
Website is advertised). If You follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these
websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies
and that COINDUMP does not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any
Personal Data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as contact and
location data. Please check these policies before You submit any personal data to these websites
or use these services.
RETAIN INFORMATION
                                                                                                   4

26. In accordance with Applicable Law and as needed to provide services to COINDUMP
Participants, COINDUMP may hold Your Personal Data. This requirement is conditioned by the
need of complying with legal obligations and resolving possible disputes. COINDUMP may retain
Your Personal Data for as long as You possess COINDUMP Tokens and/or use the Website or the
COINDUMP App. Moreover, Your Personal Data may be hold beyond the abovementioned period
till it is indispensable for COINDUMP to have relevant information to respond to any issues that
may arise later.
SECURITY
27. COINDUMP uses relevant electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the privacy of the
information the Participant provides to COINDUMP from loss, misuse, disclosure, alteration and
destruction. Please note that transmission of data or information (including communications by e-
mail) over the Internet or other publicly accessible networks is not one hundred percent secure.
Please note that COINDUMP are not liable for the security of any data Participants are
transmitting over the Internet, or third party content.
CHANGE/UPDATE/DELETE PERSONAL DATA
28. You have a right to demand COINDUMP to provide You access to Your Personal Data and to
require the correction, updating or deletion of incorrect or/and inaccurate data by contacting
COINDUMP. Nevertheless, this request must comply with COINDUMP General Terms & Conditions
of COINDUMP Tokens Sale and COINDUMP legal obligations.
AMENDMENTS
29. COINDUMP reserves the right to modify or amend this Policy at its own discretion.
If such modifications or amendments will occur, COINDUMP shall notify the Participants.
Your continued usage of the Website shall mean Your acceptance of those modifications
and amendments.
                                                                                             5
